let questionBank = [
  {question:"This country's Kukur Tihar Festival celebrates dogs and their loyal, intimate relationship with us",
  answer1:"China",
  answer2:"Nepal",
  answer3:"Saudi Arabia",
  answer4:"Korea",
  answer5:"Oman",
  correctAns:"Nepal"
  },
  {question:"Where was Napoleon crowned Emperor of Europe in 1804?",
  answer1:"The Duomo in Milan, Italy",
  answer2:"The Brandenburg Gate in Berlin, Germany",
  answer3:"The Golden Gate Bridge in San Francisco, USA",
  answer4:"The Notre Dame Cathedral in Paris, France",
  answer5:"The Great Wall Of China, China",
  correctAns:"The Notre Dame Cathedral in Paris, France"
  },
  {question:"The Taj Mahal is located in which city/country?",
  answer1:"New York, USA",
  answer2:"Uttar Pradesh, India",
  answer3:"Manila, Philippines",
  answer4:"Rome, Italy",
  answer5:"Beijing, China",
  correctAns:"Uttar Pradesh, India"
  },
  {question:"This country hosts the Harbin festival, which is the largest snow and ice festival in the world. Featuring carvings over 20 feet and full-size buildings made from giant blocks of ice",
  answer1:"China",
  answer2:"Russia",
  answer3:"North Korea",
  answer4:"Greenland",
  answer5:"Scotland",
  correctAns:"China"
  },
  {question:"The Island of Madagascar is located to the east of which continent?",
  answer1:"Asian",
  answer2:"Indian",
  answer3:"African",
  answer4:"South American",
  answer5:"North American",
  correctAns:"African"
  },
  {question:"The European Union HQ is located in which country?",
  answer1:"England",
  answer2:"Germany",
  answer3:"Belgium",
  answer4:"Poland",
  answer5:"Lithuania",
  correctAns:"Belgium"
  },
  {question:"This country hosts the Cooper Hill's Cheese Rolling Festival - where hundreds of men run down a hill while chasing a wheel of cheese",
  answer1:"England",
  answer2:"Germany",
  answer3:"Belgium",
  answer4:"Poland",
  answer5:"Ireland",
  correctAns:"England"
  },
  {question:"Big Ben is a world-famous clock-tower located in which city?",
  answer1:"Dublin",
  answer2:"London",
  answer3:"Beijing",
  answer4:"Pyongyang",
  answer5:"Morocco",
  correctAns:"London"
  },
  {question:"The tallest building in the world can be found in which country?",
  answer1:"USA",
  answer2:"China",
  answer3:"Saudi Arabia",
  answer4:"Israel",
  answer5:"Oman",
  correctAns:"Saudi Arabia"
  },
  {question:"Which country holds one of the 8 wonders of the world - a volcano that's known for its perfect cone-shape?",
  answer1:"Japan",
  answer2:"Philippines",
  answer3:"Spain",
  answer4:"Chile",
  answer5:"New Zealand",
  correctAns:"Philippines"
  }
  ];